

# Fernando del Río Figueira

UX/UI Designer | Full-Stack Developer

+34 695 267 044

Maria f.delrio.figueira@gmail.com

in Fernando del Río Figueira

#### About me

I consider myself as an ambitious and creative person, looking forward to expanding my learning.

I am specialized in UX/UI, creating data-driven digital products. I am experienced in researching to find the best solution for a given case scenario considering all the possible constraints.

From my perspective, IT professionals should be in constant evolution. Which is why I decided to enhance my profile by acquiring development skills in order to understand and participate in most of the process involved in creating a digital product.

### **Skills**

Figma	Adobe Suite
Interaction Design	UI Design
User Research	Prototyping
Usability testing	Info. Architecture
Data Analysis	HTML 5   CSS 3
NodeJS	Angular
React 18	MongoDB
MySQL	

### Experience

Jul 2023 - Jun 2024

UX/UI Designer (Talentum Internship)

Telefónica S.A.

Feb 2023 - Apr 2023

Product Designer (Work placement)

Rebase T.N.

## Languages

Spanish (Native) English (B2)

Galician (Native) French (B1)

#### Education

Jul 2024 - Sep 2024

Full-Stack Development Bootcamp

O Upgrade Hub (Madrid)

Sep 2019 - May 2023

Degree in Graphic Design

🧿 🛮 EASD Ramón Falcón (Lugo)

Sep 2017 - Jun 2019

Baccalaureate (Social Sciences)

 IES Rosalía de Castro (Santiago de Compostela)